See him before he sees you.
Tom Horn is a western, action, drama film directed by William Wiard.
A renowned former army scout is hired by ranchers to hunt down rustlers but finds himself
on trial for the murder of a boy when he carries out his job too well.
Tom Horn finds that the simple skills he knows are of no help in dealing with the ambitions of
ranchers and corrupt officials as progress marches over him and the old west.
Tom Horn, played by Steve McQueen.
Glendolene Kimmel, played by Linda Evans.
John Coble, played by Richard Farnsworth.
Joe Belle, played by Billy Green Bush.
Sam Creedmore, played by Slim Pickens.
Assistant Prosecutor, played by Peter Canon.
Tom Horn is a 1980 American Western film directed by William Wiard and starring
Steve McQueen as the legendary lawman, outlaw and gunfighter Tom Horn.
It was based on Horn's own writings.
The film explores themes of hero, ranch, trial, shootout, one man army.
The tone is dark and emotional.